let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which programming language is widely used for developing Android mobile applications?",
    answer: "Java",
    options: [
      "Python",
      "Java",
      "Ruby",
      "Swift"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which operating system is not based on the Linux kernel?",
    answer: "macOS",
    options: [
      "Ubuntu",
      "macOS",
      "Android",
      "CentOS",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following data structures is used for implementing recursion?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Stack",
      "Queue",
      "Linked List",
      "Tree",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which algorithm is used for sorting an array in ascending order?",
    answer: "BubbleSort",
    options: [
      "QuickSort",
      "MergeSort",
      "BubbleSort",
      "HeapSort",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What does SQL stand for?",
    answer: "Structured Query Language",
    options: [
      "Stylish Question Language",
      "Stylesheet Query Language",
      "Statement Question Language",
      "Structured Query Language"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the maximum theoretical speed of USB 3.0?",
    answer: "10 Gbps",
    options: [
     "1 Gbps",
     "5 Gbps",
     "10 Gbps",
     "100 Gbps",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following protocols is used for secure communication over the internet?",
    answer: " HTTPS",
    options: [
      "HTTP",
      "SMTP",
      "FTP",
      "HTTPS",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following data structures is based on the principle of Last In First Out (LIFO)?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
    "Stack",
    "Queue",
    "Linked List",
    "Tree",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which software is used for version control and collaboration among software developers?",
    answer: "Git",
    options: [
     "Microsoft Excel",
     "Google Drive",
     "Git",
     "Adobe Photoshop",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which programming language is used for building web applications?",
    answer: "JavaScript",
    options: [
      "Java",
      "Python",
      "JavaScript",
      "C++",
    ]
  },
];